Inside of our AddEntry.js file,
在 AddEntry.js 文件中
we have this reset method,
有一个这样的 reset 方法
and we also have the submit method.
还有一个 submit 方法
You'll notice that we have notes here about
你会发现在这里有一些注释
what we're eventually going to do in both of these methods,
注明了我们将在这两个方法中执行的任务
and one of these is save to our database.
其中一个任务是将数据保存到数据库中
So we have that right there,
在这里
and then we also have that right there and databases and
还有在这里
quotations because we're going to be using basically
数据库用引号引起来了
AsyncStorage or react-native's local storage
因为我们将使用 AsyncStorage 即 react-native 的本地存储组件
component to kind of pretend that we have a database.
假装我们有一个数据库
So what we'll do in this video,
在本视频中
let's go ahead and build out our api.js file so we can
我们将构建 api.js 文件
update line 70 right here as well as line 81.
以便执行第 70 行和 81 行注明的任务
So inside of our utils folder,
在 utils 文件夹中
let's make a new api.js file.
新建一个 api.js 文件
And in here, the very first thing that we're going to need as I
在此文件中 首先需要导入
just mentioned is AsyncStorage,
之前提到的 AsyncStorage
which is coming from react-native.
它来自于 react-native
And then another thing we're going to grab is this right here,
然后需要获取的是
our CALENDAR_STORAGE_KEY which is basically just where we're
这个文件里的 CALENDAR_STORAGE_KEY
going to persist the information inside of our AsyncStorage.
我们将在其中存储 AsyncStorage 中的信息
So we will grab that from our calendar file right here that was given to us.
从这个路径下的 calendar 文件中获取
And so now, we're going to have two different methods or two different functions.
现在我们将用到两种不同的方法 即两种函数
The very first one, we will call submitEntry,
第一个叫做 submitEntry
and the second one is going to be removeEntry.
第二个叫做 removeEntry
So we have submit,
提交和删除功能创建好了
remove, and so right here,
在这里
when we submit, we're going to call our submit function that we're making.
当我们提交时 将调用我们要创建的提交函数
And then right here, we will call remove.
在这里 将调用删除函数
So let's go ahead and do submit first.
先创建提交函数
What we're going to pass it is an object that has
向其传入一个对象
the specific entry on it as well as the key.
它具有特定的 entry 和 key
And then what we will do is we will call AsyncStorage.mergeItem.
然后调用 AsyncStorage.mergeItem
So we're going to pass it, CALENDAR_STORAGE_KEY,
传入 CALENDAR_STORAGE_KEY
and then what we're going to merge into it is a stringified version of this object,
合并的内容是该对象的 stringify 版本
which has the key as the property name and the entry as the value.
key 是属性名称 entry 是值
So again, what we're doing here is we're submitting a new entry for the day,
这里是为当天提交新的条目
and what we want to do is we want to take that entry and add it to
我们想要将该条目添加到数据库中
our database or our AsyncStorage on the phone,
也就是手机上的 AsyncStorage
and we will do that using mergeItems.
方法是使用 mergeItem
So we will merge this object right here into this property on our AsyncStorage.
我们将该对象合并到 AsyncStorage 中的这个属性上
And then for removeEntry,
对于 removeEntry
what we're going to do is we will pass it a key,
向其传入一个 key
and now what we want to do is we want to remove
然后从 AsyncStorage 中
the item at this key from our AsyncStorage.
删除位于这个 key 的项目
So let's go ahead and we will say return AsyncStorage.
输入 return AsyncStorage.
First, we are going to get everything at this location,
首先获取这个位置的所有信息
and then once we have this information,
获得这些信息后
let's just call it results,
称之为 results
then what we will do is let's parse it.
然后解析该信息
And then we are going to say that data[key] is going to be undefined,
输入 data[key] = undefined
so I'm sure there is a better way to do this, but this will work.
肯定还有更好的方式 不过这样也可行
Now, we're going to delete the data[key].
现在删除 data[key]
So basically, just saying grab all that information,
也就是获取所有这些信息
delete whatever's at this key property,
删除该 key 属性所在位置的所有信息
and then use AsyncStorage.setItem
然后使用 AsyncStorage.setItem
to say CALENDAR_STORAGE_KEY or all these stuff at CALENDAR_STORAGE_KEY
并输入 CALENDAR_STORAGE_KEY 即位于 CALENDAR_STORAGE_KEY 的所有信息
is going to be all of our data after
将为删除该特定键所对应位置的项目
we've removed the item at that specific key and after we have stringified it.
及对信息 stringify 之后的所有数据
And so now, what we want to do is we want to
现在我们将在 AddEntry 中
call both of these functions inside of AddEntry.
调用这两个函数
So up here, let's go ahead and import both of them.
在顶部导入这两个函数
We had submitEntry as well as removeEntry.
即 submitEntry 和 removeEntry
And then what we want to do is down here,
然后在下面的 submit 中
instead of submit, we can delete this line and we can call submitEntry.
我们删掉这行并调用 submitEntry
Remember, we're passing an object that has the key which is just going to
我们要传入的对象具有一个 key
be whatever timeToString gives us as well as our entry,
该 key 是 timeToString 提供给我们的信息
which is just the local states.
以及 entry 是本地状态
And then down here, inside of reset.
然后在下面的 reset 中
we are going to call removeEntry passing it the key, which,
我们将调用 removeEntry 传入一个 key
again, is just coming from whatever timeToString gives us.
它也来自于 timeToString 提供给我们的信息